A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 1, 1946-1969; 1936-1984; 1; 97.21 Cubic Feet 251 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 1-94.
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - General Correspondence, 1946-1965 (Box 136, Folder 1-4, Box 137, Folder 1)
    LSR and DR investment. RBM, CHB, POC, HW, TFW, CES, CBS.
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - From CES, 1957-1958 (Box 137, Folder 2-4)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Brochures (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Annual Reports (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Agreements (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Business Machines, 1956 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Brokerage Reports, 1954-1963 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc., 1954-1963 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Contract Status Reports, 1950-1960 (Box 138, Folder 3, Box 139, Folder 4, Box 140, Folder 1-2, Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Corporate Documents (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Agreements (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Corporate Meetings, 1954-1958 (Box 141, Folder 4-5)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Directors Meetings, 1946-1963 (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Executive Committee, 1946-1959 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financial, 1946-1950 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Reports to Executive Committee, 1951-1957 (Box 143, Folder 1-2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financial - Budgets, 1949-1956 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financing - Programs, 1946-1950 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financing - Forecasts, 1956-1963 (Box 144, Folder 2-3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financial - Comparisons, 1952-1962 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financial - Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financial - Reviews, 1956-1961 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Independent Research, 1955 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Air Force Survey Team, 1957 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Instruments for Science, 1953 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - International Division, 1959-1961 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Memoranda, 1947-1959 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - General, 1957-1961 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - Business Machines Corp., 1957-1958 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - Eastern Industries, 1961 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - Tracer Labs, 1960-1961 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - General, 1955-1956 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    National Union Electronic. General Precision Equipment.
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - Servo-Mechanisms, 1959 (Box 146, Folder 5, Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Financing - Rockefeller Interest, 1952 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Mergers - Teleregister Electronics (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Production Control Review, 1955 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Programs for Operations, 1955 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Prospectus, 1954-1960 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Progress Reports, 1958-1963 (Box 148, Folder 1-4, Box 149)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Reports, 1951-1955 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    Blodgett. Eberstat. Background
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Stock Options, 1958-1960 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Stock Interests, 1962 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Stock Holders - Meetings, 1958-1963 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Stock Interests - V Loan, 1957-1960 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Stock Holders - Note Holders, 1961 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Material from CES Office, 1956-1963 (Box 150, Folder 5, Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory for Electronics - Material from David Rockefeller Office, 1956-1963 (Box 151, Folder 2-3)
  - Laboratory for Electronics, Inc. - Summary, 1947-1964 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - La Fleur Corp., 1961-1963 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    Cryogenics company. Investigation of potential. No investment.
  - Laguana Scientific Industries, 1961-1965 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    Produce epoxy adhesive. Investment by 30 Rockefeller Plaza Associates. Difficulties, sale of company to "Locktite".
  - Le Baron, Robert, 1954-1964 (Box 152, Folder 3-4)
    Hired to make a continuing study for one year of commercial potential of atomic energy by a group of 14. Arrangement cancelled after a year. Reports on findings. No real commercial potentialities discussed.
  - Lithomat Corp., 1948-1949 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    Investigation of corporation. Possible investment. Decision not to invest.
  - McCarthy, Glenn, 1947-1956 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    Texas oilman. Financial status. Petroleum resources. Efforts to borrow money from LSR.
  - McCormack, James Jr., 1959-1965 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    Hired by RBI as a consultant on possible investments. Served as board member of LSR venture companies with Edward Teller. Became VP of MIT and severed connections with office.
  - McDonnell Aircraft - General Correspondence, 1947-1960 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    LSR investment in McDonnell company. Company progress. Changes in LSR investment. Differing business philosophy.
  - McDonnell Aircraft - Annual Reports, 1948-1959 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - McDonnell Aircraft - Financing, 1948-1949 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - McDonnell Aircraft - Stock Interests, 1948-1959 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - McDonnell Aircraft - Summary, undated (Box 154, Folder 2-3)
  - McLean, Ethel, 1950-1951 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    WR guaranteed bank loan for Miss McLean, a sculptress.
  - MHD Research, Inc. (Box 154, Folder 5, Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Macalaster Scientific Corp., 1961-1966 (Box 155, Folder 2-3)
    Purchase of stock in Macalaster-Bricknell Corporation. Manufacturer of laboratory supplies. Change of name, new financing, sale of divisions. Purchase by Raytheon in 1965.
  - John P. Maquire Co. (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Malaker Laboratories, 1961-1965 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    Manufacturer of cryogenic equipment. No Rockefeller interest.
  - Marine Aircraft Corp., 1950-1953 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    LSR investment commitment never completed. Bankruptcy. Richard E. Byrd, LSR, HW.
  - Marquardt - General, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 1-4)
    LSR investment. Management. Mergers. Final merger with CCI.
  - Marquardt - Directors Correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Marquardt - Directors Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 157, Folder 1-3)
  - Marquardt - Directors Meetings, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 1-3, Box 159)
  - Marquardt - Directors Meetings, 1965-1967 (Box 160, Folder 1-3)
  - Marquardt - Directors Meetings, 1968 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Marquardt - Executive Committee, 1950-1966 (Box 161, Folder 2-3)
  - Marquardt - Purchase Agreements (Box 161, Folder 4-5, Box 162, Folder 1-2)
  - Marquardt - Candidates for New President, 1964 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Marquart - Contract Status (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Marquardt - Credit Agreements, 1950-1958 (Box 162, Folder 5, Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Marquardt - European Activities (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Marquardt - Facilities, 1948-1956 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Marquardt - Family Stock Interest, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Marquardt - Financing, 1950-1958 (Box 163, Folder 5-6, Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Marquardt - Financial - Office Reviews, 1949-1956 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Marquardt - By-Laws (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Marquardt - Inter-Company Memos, 1962-1968 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Marquardt - Mergers (Box 166, Folder 1-5)
  - Marquardt - Mergers (Box 167, Folder 1-13)
  - Marquardt - Purchase Agreement, 1956 (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - Marquardt - Public Relations, 1951-1956 (Box 168, Folder 1-3)
  - Marquardt - Research and Development, 1950-1959 (Box 168, Folder 4-6)
  - Marquardt - Stockholders Lists, 1950-1954 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Marquardt - Subcontracts (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Marquardt - West Coast Trip, 1954-1961 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Marquardt - Letters from Stockholders, 1961-1964 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Marquardt - Shareholders, 1952-1968 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Marquardt - Stock Options, 1957-1968 (Box 169, Folder 3-4)
  - Marquardt - Corporate Planning, 1952-1961 (Box 170, Folder 1-4)
  - Marquardt - Summary, undated (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Martin, Glenn L., Co., 1947-1954 (Box 296, Folder 2-3)
    Construction of cargo aircraft. HW, LSR, H.P. Driscoll.
  - Mass Market Publications, Inc., 1950-1956 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    Publishers of BETTER LIVING magazine distributed through the Super Market Institute. LSR, RBM.
  - Mass Market Publications, Inc. - Clippings, 1950-1956 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - Mechtron Corp., 1961-1964 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    Electronic and electro-mechanical engineering specialists. Contracts awarded. Stock purchase in 1962 by 30 Rockefeller Plaza Associates. Merger with Electromagnetic Industries, Inc. in 1964. RHS, RHW, RBM.
  - Merchants Fire Assurance Corp., 1947-1961 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    Fire, motor vehicle, ocean marine, inland navigation & transportation, extended coverage, aircraft & storm insurance. LSR member of Board until 1955. LSR, HW.
  - Middle Witwatersrand, 1948-1953 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    Gold mining in South Africa. American.Anglo-Transvaal Corp. DR Investment.
  - Mithras, Inc. - Summary, 1961-1967 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1961-1965 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Audits, 1961-1965 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Mithras, Inc. - By-Laws, Certificate of Incorporation, 1961-1965 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Mithras, Inc. - CAB Opinion Letter, 1961-1962 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Financing, 1961-1965 (Box 298, Folder 3-4)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Contract Status, 1962-1967 (Box 171, Folder 1-2)
  - Mithras, Inc. - GLOW Contract (AMICOM), 1964-1966 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Directors Meetings, 1961-1967 (Box 171, Folder 4-5, Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Facilities (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Financial, 1961-1967 (Box 172, Folder 3-4, Box 173, Folder 1-3)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Stockholders Meetings, 1961-1967 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Stock Option Committee, 1962-1967 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Stock Plans, Options, Meetings, 1961-1966 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Mithras, Inc. - General (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Memoranda - Mergers, 1963-1966 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Mergers, 1963-1968 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Mergers - Spectra-Physics, Inc., 1966 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Mithras, Inc. - C.W. Newhall Report, 1962 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - James D. Mooney, Jr., 1964-1965 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Mithras, Inc. - Brochures, 1961-1966 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Music Press, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 175, Folder 2-4)
    Music publishers, purchased by Mercury Music Corp. in 1949. RBM, DR.
  - National Astro Labs - Articles of Incorporation (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - National Astro Labs - Audits (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - National Astro Labs - Directors Meetings, 1962-1967 (Box 175, Folder 7, Box 176, Folder 1)
  - National Astro Labs - Financing, 1961-1968 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - National Astro Labs - General, 1961-1966 (Box 176, Folder 3, Box 177, Folder 1)
    Activities in field of calibration, also produce electronic components. POC, CHB, TFW, LSR.
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers - Bowmar Instrument Corp., 1962-1964 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers - Reed and Reese, 1961-1964 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers - Detroit Testing Lab (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers - Semiconductor Magnetics (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers - Techniserv Corp. (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - National Astro Labs - Mergers - Metrolonics Association (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - National Aviation Corporation - Purchases and Sales, 1963-1968 (Box 178, Folder 1-3, Box 179, Folder 1-2)
  - National Aviation Corporation - Directors Meetings, 1963-1966 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - National Aviation Corporation - Executive Meetings, 1963-1966 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - National Bank of Westchester, 1955-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1-2)
    LSR, JEL, JRD, CBS, DR.
  - National Fuels Corporation, 1949-1961 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - National Old Line Insurance Co., 1956 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    No investment. WR was director. RHM, WJM, WR.
  - Naval Air Advisory Council, 1946-1965 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    Peace time advisoty association with Bureau of Aeronautics for some of those who served with it during the war. LSR participation until 1953 when he resigned his commission in USNR.
  - National State Bank of Newark, 1964 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    Capital notes offered, purchased by RBI. PB.
  - New England Nuclear Corp. - Financing, 1961-1963 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    Produces radioactive chemicals. POC, RBM, TFW, RHS.
  - New England Nuclear Corp. - Initial Planning, 1961 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - New England Nuclear Corp. - Publicity, 1961-1964 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Needham and Grohmann, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    Advertising agency. Handles promotion for Colonial Williamsburg, Rockefeller Center, and resorts. Inquiry re Eastern Airlines account. HW, AB.
  - New York Airways - General, 1949-1962 (Box 182, Folder 1-3)
    Helicopter service. Investment made. LSR, DR, HW, F.H. Driscoll, RBM, CHB, N.E. Halaby.
  - New York Airways - Air Traffic Control System, 1959 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - New York Airways - CAB Loan Guarantee, 1960 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - New York Airways - Crudge Report, 1962 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - New York Airways - Stock Interest, 1951-1962 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - New York Airways - Financial Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - New York City - Civil Defense, 1954-1967 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    Civil defense conferences. LSR contribution to Civil Air Patrol. TFW, ENH, LSR, RBM.
  - New York Society of Security Analysts, 1955-1964 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    Members of RBI staff attend luncheons and conferences. Dues. CHB, PB.
  - New York World's Fair, 1964-1966 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    Rockefeller Center, Inc. investment in promisory notes. HW, DR.
  - North American Co., 1947-1961 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    Public utility holding company. Mrs. LSR holdings. MFR, A.W. Hastings, KAW.
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - General, 1954-1961 (Box 184, Folder 5-6)
    Nuclear engineering company performing basic and applied research and development and engaging in engineering design for Government and industry. DR, LSR, TFW, RBM, HW.
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Board of Directors - Correspondence and Meetings, 1954-1960 (Box 184, Folder 7-8, Box 185, Folder 1-4)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - By-laws, 1956 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Facilities, 1956 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - Audits, 1954-1960 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - Budgets, 1958-1959 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - Forecasts, 1960 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - Organization Charts, 1956 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - Monthly Statements, 1956 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financial Reviews, 1958-1960 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - 5 Year Expansion, 1956 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing - Backlog, 1956 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Inter-Company Memos, 1960 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Summary, 1961 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Merger Discussions, 1955-1960 (Box 186, Folder 8-10)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Board of Directors, 1961 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financial Letter Agreement, 1954 August 18 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Financing Letter Agreement, 1956 January 11 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Annual Reports, 1955-1961 (Box 187, Folder 4-5)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Private Financing, 1957 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Product Planning and Development, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Public Relations, 1952-1960 (Box 188, Folder 3-4)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Stock Interests, 1955-1960 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Stock Options, 1957-1961 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Training Reactor Program, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Nuclear Development-Europe, 1957 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Nuclear Consolidated Edison, 1958-1960 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Otis Elevator, 1956-1959 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Development Corp. - Belgian Congo, 1957 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Materials and Equipment Corp., 1958-1963 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Perrine Industries, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    Manufacturers of glass products. DR investment, sold stock in 1964. DR, PB.
  - Piasecki Aircraft, 1949-1964 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Piasecki Helicopters - General, 1945-1955 (Box 189, Folder 7, Box 190, Folder 1)
    Research, design, development and production of aeronautical products; some subcontracting work. LSR investment. LSR, HW, CHB, TFW.
  - Piasecki Helicopters - Financial, 1945-1949 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Piasecki Helicopters - Stock Interests, 1946-1948 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Pinturas Tucan, S.A., 1954-1955 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    Manufacturers of paint. Rockefeller Center, Inc. stock purchase. JEL, W.S. Miller.
  - Pioche Mines Consolidated, 1958-1959 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    Mary Clark Rockefeller investment. PB.
  - Puenta Alegre Sugar, 1957-1963 (Box 190, Folder 6, Box 191, Folder 1-2)
    Holding company for three Cuban and four American sugar companies. DR on board of directors. PB, CHB, S.R. Peale.
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - General, 1947-1948 (Box 191, Folder 3-4)
    Rocket engine research. LSR investment. LSR.
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Closing Papers, 1947 (Box 192, Folder 1-2)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Directors Correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Merger Discussions, 1948-1959 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Mergers - Olin Mathieson, 1953-1957 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Stock Interests - General, 1950-1958 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Stock Interests - Olin Mathieson Purchase, 1953 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Stock Participation, undated (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Stock Participation - McDonnell Aircraft, 1947 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Stock and Voting Trust Certificate Record, 1947-1950 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Prospectus, 1949 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Reaction Motors, Inc. - Summary, 1947-1958 (Box 193, Folder 5-6)
  - Republic Aviation Corp., 1948-1965 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    Manufacture aircraft. LSR investment. HW.
  - Scantlin Electronics - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Scantlin Electronics - Directors Meetings, 1958-1965 (Box 194, Folder 3-4)
    Design, development and manufacture of electronic devices for commerce and industry. Investment made. RBM, RGC, WJM.
  - Scientific Atlanta, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    Microfilm development, electronics development, instrument cases. R.H. Strange was director. Includes minutes of directors meetings and stock plans. RHS.
  - Seaboard and Western Airlines. Inc. - CAB Approval, 1960-1961 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Seaboard and Western Airlines. Inc. - Financing, 1960-1963 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    LSR holdings. HW.
  - Seaboard and Western Airlines, Inc. - Refinancing, 1960 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Second Stage Capital Corp., 1964 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Shipshape Co., 1960 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    Distributor of liquid detergent. Loan guaranteed by LSR. REM.
  - Shockley, Dr. William, 1955-1957 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    Consultant on electronics during 1955.
  - SIDRO, 1953-1960 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    Societe Internationale d'Energie Hydro-Electrique. Holding company controlled by Sofina (Belgian utility group). DR and LSR investment. RBM.
  - Squaw Valley Development Corp. - General, 1948-1953 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Squaw Valley Development Corp. - Financial, 1948-1953 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Squaw Valley Development Corp. - Alexander Cushing, 1948-1953 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Squaw Valley Development Corp. - Maps and Photographs, 1948-1953 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Squaw Valley Development Corp. - Directors Meetings, 1950 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Squaw Valley Development Corp. - Loan, 1948-1953 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - South Shore Oil and Development, 1954-1968 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    Located in Louisiana and Texas. Mary Clark Rockefeller holdings. IT, GPM.
  - Squire-Sanders - Directors Meetings, 1963-1967 (Box 196, Folder 5, Box 197, Folder 1-2, Box 198, Folder 1)
    Manufacture radio equipment. Name changed to Computone, Inc. Investment made. WJM, RBM
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1952-1963 (Box 198, Folder 2-4)
    R.H. Strange is associate. RHS, TFW, CBS.
  - Stavid Engineering, 1953-1962 (Box 199, Folder 1-2)
    Design and manufacture of electronic equipment and offer engineering and technical service in installation and maintenance of electromechanical equipemtn. Investment made. RBM, HW, DR, LSR.
  - Strange, Robert H., 1960-1965 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    Miscellaneous correspondence. Mineral Exploration
  - Taleott, James - Directors Meetings, 1963-1967 (Box 199, Folder 4, Box 200, Folder 1)
    Commercial financing company. H.W. is a director.
  - Taxes - General, 1962 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Taxes - Interest Equalization, 1963-1964 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Taxes - Excess Profits, 1950-1962 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Taxes - Revenue Acts, 1952-1963 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Templeton Growth Fund of Canada, Ltd., 1954 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    Proposed non-resident owned investment company in Canada. LSR investment. RHM.
  - Terrinca, 1957-1964 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    Corporation formed to acquire and develop unimproved real estate in the Quatira Valley near Caracas, Venezuela. DR investment. WTL, DR.
  - Thermo-Electron Engineering Corp. - Directors Meetings, 1960-1964 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    Manufacture and research in field of power of thermionic conversion. LSR investment.
  - Thermo-Electron Engineering Corp. - C.l. Newhall Report, 1963 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Thermo-Electron Engineering Corp. - Organization Chart, 1963 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Thiokol Chemical - General, 1958-1964 (Box 201, Folder 4-5, Box 202, Folder 1)
    Fuel and rubber research and development. TFW, CHB.
  - Thiokol Chemical - Directors Meetings, 1961-1966 (Box 202, Folder 2-3, Box 203, Folder 1-2)
  - Thiokol Chemical - Directors Data Books, 1961-1964 (Box 203, Folder 3, Box 204, Folder 1-4, Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Thiokol Chemical - Divisions, 1959-1964 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    National Electonics Lab, Hunter-Bristol and Wasatch.
  - Thiokol Chemical - Divisions - Holland Roller Coater, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 3)